Guide to the Vice Provost for Land Grant Affairs records,1981-2008.
Vice Provost for Land Grant Affairs records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Vice Provost for Land Grant Affairs records, 1981-2008.
4-13-3427
Cornell University. Vice Provost for Land Grant Affairs.
5.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Printed Materials, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes Francille Firebaugh's correspondence, speeches and presentations, committee material and university related material.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes Francille Firebaugh's correspondence, speeches and presentations, committee material and university related material.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Firebaugh, Francille M., 1933-; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Faculty.; State University of New York.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the office origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, December 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correpsondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correpsondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2000-December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2001-December 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, Jan. 2002-Dec. 2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2002-December 2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Alumni Correspondence for Hum Ec Reunion, July 18, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-Decenber 2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2003-December 2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, January 2004-December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- New Faculty Orientations, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- New Faculty Orientations, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- New Faculty Orientations, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- New Department Chair Orientations, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- New Department Chair Orientations, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- New Department Chair Orientations, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Department Chair Session, Spring 2000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Department Chair Session 1 & 2, Fall 2000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Department Chair Session 1 & 2, Fall 2000 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Department Chair Session 3, Spring 2001 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Department Chair Session, Fall 2001 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Department Chair Session, Spring 2002 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Department Chair Session, Fall 2002 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Department Chair Session, Spring 2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Department Chair Session, Fall 2003 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Department Chair Session, Spring 2004 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Department Chair Session, Fall 2004 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- New Faculty Orientation, Fall 2004 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- New Department Chair Orientation, Fall 2004 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Department Chair Session, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- New Faculty Orientation, Fall 2005 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- New Department Chair Orientation, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Department Chair Session, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Annual Reports-Firebaugh, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Speeches and Presentations-Firebaugh, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Speeches and Presentations-Firebaugh, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Speeches and Presentations-Firebaugh, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Speeches and Presentations-Firebaugh, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Speeches and Presentations-Firebaugh, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Speeches and Presentations-Firebaugh, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Speeches and Presentations-Firebaugh, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Chapters and Papers by F. Firebaugh, 1996-2005 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Statutory College Deans Meeting, February 5, 1997-May 6, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Statutory College Deans Meeting, June 24, 1998-July 7, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Statutory College Deans Meeting, August 11, 1999-November 3, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Contract College Deans Meeting, January 5, 2000-March 13, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Contract College Deans Meeting, March 16, 2001-August 14, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Contract College Deans Meeting, August 21, 2001-October 16, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Contract College Deans Meeting, October 24, 2001-December 18, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Contract College Deans Meeting, January 29, 2002-September 24, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Contract College Deans Meeting, September 26, 2002-February 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Contract College Deans Meeting, March 25, 2003-December 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Contract College Assoc. Deans/Business Officers, January 2002-August 23, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Contract College Assoc. Deans/Business Officers, August 28, 2002-December 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Contract College Coordinating Committee, January 2002-July 15, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Contract College Coordinating Committee, August 2002-May 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Contract College Coordinating Committee, July 25, 2003-November 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Bridging the Rift Foundation (BTR)-Groundbreaking Event, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 0)
- BTR Correspondence, 2000-2005 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- BTR-Agreements, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- BTR-Meetings, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- BTR-Newsletters, 2001-2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Child Care Policy for Graduate Students, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Cornell-Ithaca Partnership (C-IP) & Community Outreach Partnership Center (COPC), 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- C-IP Community Advisory Committee, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- C-IP Cornell/Ithaca Committee, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- C-IP Southside Community Center Computer Lab, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Donor Relations, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Donors-Eissner, Judith, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Donors-Gomer, Adelaide, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Donors-Good, Laura, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Donors-Reichenbach, Inge, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Donors-Seltzer, Sam, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Donors-Dunton, Craig, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Gatekeepers, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Gender and Space Allocation, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Glamour Gals, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Iscol Family Program for Leadership Development in Public Service, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Light in Winter, 2004/2003 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Light in Winter, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Ohio State University-External Review Outreach and Engagement Initiative, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Reno, Janet, 2003/2004 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Sciencenter, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Social Sciences Initiative, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Turkey, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- UCLA-Family-Centered Community Development, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Unionization, 2001/2002 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Visitors Pusan National Univ., Korea, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Visitors-Marie Lavallard, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Visitors-Chinese Institute for Nutritional Sciences, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Visitors-Jorge Ramos, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Visitors-Liz Moore, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Visitors-Hugh Gallo Dinner, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Community Foundation of Tompkins County, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- International Federation of Home Economics Congress, (IFHE) Ghana, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- International Household & Family Research Conference, Helsinki, Finland, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Land Grant Mission Review (LGMR) Implementation Plans, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- LGMR Implementation Plans, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- LGMR President's Oversight Commission, January 2002-June 2002 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- LGMR President's Oversight Commission, July 2002-January 2003 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- LGMR Formation of Charge to Panel, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- LGMR Formation of Charge to Panel, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- LGMR Publicity, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- LGMR General Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- LGMR Land Grant Panel Membership, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- LGMR Panel:CALS, Human Ecology, VetMed, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- LGMR Panel: Engineering, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- LGMR Panel:ILR, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- LGMR Panel:K-12 Education, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- LGMR Panel:Technology Transfer, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Land Grant Mission Review, October 2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Land Grant Mission Review, January 2003 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  final version
- Advancing Cornell as New York State's Land Grant University - Publication, May 2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Bailey Plaza- Committee, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Bailey Plaza- Design / Construction, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Bailey Plaza- Donors, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Bailey Plaza- General, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Bailey Plaza-History, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Bailey Plaza-Neighborhood Meetings, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Bailey Plaza-Perimeter Study, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Bailey Plaza-Photos/Publicity, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Bailey Plaza-Plaza Opening, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Annual Reports- Firebaugh6-11, 2001-2007 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Correspondence for Francille Firebaugh, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Bio/Vitae-Francille Firebaugh, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 12)